hello and welcome to new everyday what
こんにちは、 新しい 日常 へようこそ
an exciting episode we've got for you
私たちがあなたのために持っているエキサイティングなエピソード
today this is our special guest Leno
今日は これが私たちの特別 ゲスト、レノです
Samuel and he's going to talk to us
サミュエルと彼は私たち と話 をします
about the healing of God the calling of
神の癒し 呼び出しの 程度
God the provision of God you won't want
神はあなたが望んでいない神の準備
to miss this
これが欠けている
this is new every day with Jeff Weston
これはJeff Westonと毎日新しいことです
and Cruz
クルーズ
[Music]
[音楽]
well hello my name is Lawrence Cruz and
こんにちは私の名前は ローレンスクルーズと
Jeff Weston is away this week but I'm
ジェフ・ウェストンは今週は離れています が、私は
back from vacation and happy to be with
休暇から戻って 、幸せになる
you today for new every day we have a
新しい毎日のために 、今日 、私たちは持っています
very special guest with us today his
私たちと今日 は非常に特別なゲスト 彼の
name is Lynn Oh Samuel and he's all the
名前はリンああサミュエルであり、彼がすべてです
way from India I'll tell you what we've
インドからの道私は、私たちが何をしたか
got lots to talk about how are you today
今日はどうですか？
Lynn oh I'm doing good thanks for having
リンはああ、私は持つ ために良いおかげでやっています
me in this show oh you're very welcome
私はこのショーであなたは 大歓迎です
it's so good that you could join us this
あなたが私たちに これに 参加できることはとても良いことです
week and I know you and I know you've
あなたと私はあなたが知っていることを知っています
got a fascinating story about the
魅力的な話を聞い た
provision of God and I can't wait to
神 と私の提供はに 待つことができません
hear all that God's gonna share with us
神様が私たちと分かち合うことをすべて聞いてください
today but tell us a little bit about
今日しかし私たち について 少し 教えて
yourself I just said you're from India
あなた自身、 私は ちょうどあなたがインド出身だと言った
dad that's a big place yes I'm from
私はから来たんだそう大きな場所 だお父さん
India from the southern part of India
インド南部のインド
the province name is called Kerala
州名はケララ
Kerala I've heard of that because I went
ケララ私はそれを聞いたので、私は行った
to India and I flew into the city called
インドに行き、私は市内に飛んだ
Hyderabad yeah it is wetted nearby yeah
ハイデラバードええそれは 近くに 濡れて いるええ
okay so that's nearby to Kerala yes that
それはケーララの近く にあります
how you say it
あなたはそれをどう言う
yeah Canela okay and I've since learned
うん、 Canela大丈夫、私はそれ以来学んだ
since since we've become friends that a
私たちが友達になったので
man that I've listened to a very
私が聞いた人
well-respected man of God is from the
神の敬虔な人は、
province of Kerala yeah his name is Ravi
ケララ州の州の名前は彼の名前はラヴィ
Zacharias is this true yeah that's true
Zachariasは本当のええこれは本当です
like are you personal friends with Robin
あなたはロビンとの個人的な友人ですか？
no I listened to him and yeah he's a
いいえ、私は 彼 に耳を傾け、 彼は
wonderful servant of God yeah absolutely
神のしもべ素晴らしいええ、絶対に
and we were talking today earlier as
私たちは今日より早く話していました
well about Thomas you didn't Thomas from
トーマスについてあなたはトーマスから来ていない
the Bible like isn't it the doubting
聖書のように疑うことではない
Thomas yeah yeah we have a long
トーマス ええ、 私たちは長い
tradition called and no send Thomas
伝統は呼ばれ、 トーマスは送らない
coming to India it is very near to my
インドに来て、それは 私の
hometown it's a one hour journey from my
故郷から私からの 1時間の 旅です
home so he came to that province and
彼は その州に来 て
that's why you know if you look to the
あなたが見れば、あなたが知っている理由です
southern part of India the Christian we
インド南部 のクリスチャン たち
can see that a large percentage of
大部分の
Christian multis
キリスト教の多
the southern pot okay and you're one of
南の鍋は 大丈夫 、あなたは
those yeah man of God who knows Christ
キリストを知っている神の人よ
as his Lord and Savior and this is a
主と救い主として、 これは
fascinating journey well tell me a
魅惑的な旅は私に
little bit about yourself your mom and a
あなた自身、あなたのお母さんとAについて少し
dad you have any brothers or sisters my
あなたには兄弟姉妹がいます。
mom and dad I was born in a Christian
お母さんとお父さん私はキリスト教徒で生まれました
family and I have one brother so my
家族と 私には1人の兄弟がいる ので
parents raised us residence up in a
両親が私たちを居住地にして
Christian faith and so growing up in a
キリスト教の信仰とは、 そうで育っ
Christian family everything was very
キリスト教の家族はす​​べて非常に
mechanical for me going to the worship
私のための機械的な崇拝に行く
service and being part of the church but
サービスと教会の一部ですが
I had a personal encounter with the Lord
私は主と個人的な出会いがありました
when I was in my 10th grade where I
私は10年生の時に どこに
committed my life for the Lord service
私の人生を主のために捧げ ました
now for me and when I was in the tenth
今私のために、私は 第十 に いたとき
grade I was 15 years of age yeah
グレード私は 15 歳でした
were you is that the same as 14 and
あなたは14歳と同じですか？
that's okay 14 well I know because
それは大丈夫です14私は知っている
you're smarter than I am so that would
私は そのためだろう 私 よりもあなたが賢くです
kind of explain it okay so really sir
一種の ように本当に大丈夫 先生が それを 説明します
two age 14 yeah 14 you had an encounter
2つの年齢 14ええ14あなたは出会いを持っていた
with God and and yeah tell me about that
神ととしてええ こと を教えて
what did he what happened
何が起こったのか
yeah the 10th grade has begun and I want
ええ、 10年生が始まり、私は欲しい
to go to the classes but suddenly I fell
クラスに行くが突然私は落ちた
ill and I was taken to the hospital
病気と私は 病院 に連れて行っ た
there was a sudden shooting up of my
私の突然の撮影があった
temperature in my body and so taken to
私の体の中の温度など
the hospital I was there for many weeks
病院私 は 何 週間 もそこにい た
and the doctors were not able to
医者はできなかった
diagnose what was happening with me and
私と何が起こっているのかを診断する
then they transferred me to another
彼らは私を別のものに移した
hospital where it's a multi-specialty
マルチスペシャルである病院
hospital where they have every
どこにいても病院
department and they have been checking
彼らはチェックしています
up with me and at the end they found out
私と一緒に 、最後に彼らは
that my white blood cell count has been
私の白血球数は
going down and which was affecting my
私のことに影響を与えていた
internal organs oh my goodness when I
内部の器官ああ私の良さ私
hear white blood count like blood cells
血液細胞のような白血球数を聞く
going down I'm no doctor but that's it
私は医者ではないが、それはそれだ
that's dangerous dangerous your organs
それは危険なあなたの器官です
were shutting down and the medicines
シャットダウンしていた薬
were not affecting the medicines were
薬に影響を与えていなかった
not respond
応答しない
in my body and they do not know what to
私の体の中で、彼らは何をすべきか分からない
do at that time they called me at the
その時 、彼らは 私を
end maybe they called my parents this is
最後には、多分彼らはこれが私の両親と呼ばれます
what I came to know through my parents
私が両親 を通して知ったこと
because I was in a critical unit and so
私は、重要なユニットとそうであった ため、
at the end after talking with the
最後に話を してから
doctors and then they allowed my mum to
医者たちは私の お母さんに
come into my room and so I also felt
私の部屋に 来て、 私も感じた
within myself that I am nearing to the
自分自身の中で私は近づいている
end of my life and there you remember
私の人生の終わりに、あなたは覚えています。
that is a 14 year old boy yeah I
それは14 歳の少年 です
remember that
それを覚えて
oh I can't imagine that must've that's
ああ、私はそれが 必然 かも しれ ないと想像することはできません
probably a terrible feeling yeah
おそらく恐ろしい感じのええ
oh and so here you think god this is it
ああ、だからここであなたは 神 だと思う
yeah this is it and so I came to realise
ええこれはそれだから私は 実現する ようになった
that my mum was crying of them near to
私のお母さんは近くに泣いていた
my bed and holding my hand and then
私のベッドと私の手を保持して
that's only a few minutes they allowed
それは許可されたほんの数分です
me and they allowed my mum to come to
私と彼らは私の お母さんが来るのを 許し た
that room so mum left and so there on
その部屋はお母さんに残っていたので、 そこにも
that bed I started to cry unto the Lord
私が主に向かって叫び始めたその寝床
a lot what is happening with my life and
私の人生で 何が 起きて いるのか
then I started to commit my life to the
私は私の人生を
Lord and I started to confess my sins
主と私は私の罪を告白し始めました
and rededicate my life to the Lord all
私の人生をすべての主に復活させる
of a sudden in the late night I started
私が始めた深夜の突然の
to experience the presence of God in my
私の中に神の存在を経験する
life and in that hospital bed room for
人生とその病院のベッドルームで
many weeks I have been like in a
私がようにされている多くの週
vegetable my body became so lean and I'm
野菜私の体はとても痩せ、私は
at the end of my life where so
私の人生の終わりに
completely on the liquid food
液体食品に完全に
there on that night as I was praying to
その夜私が祈っていたときに
God in a very supernatural way I started
私が始めた非常に超自然的な方法で神
to experience the presence of God in
神の存在を経験する
that room okay oh my goodness I am
その部屋は 大丈夫ですよ 、私の良さは私です
fascinated here we're talking about the
ここに魅了されたのは、
provision of God but we're hearing about
神の準備ができていますが、私たちは
something so much with so much depth of
そんなに深い
a healing of the Lord I understand it
主の癒しを理解する
yeah well I getting is also publishing
ええ、私もまた出版しています
them all there
それらすべて そこに
provision of god and it certainly is and
神の準備とそれは確かに
so yet there's so much more to your
あなたにはまだまだたくさんのことがあります
story but this is fascinating soul in oh
物語が、オハイオ州の魅力的な魂です
you you you cry out to God in in a
あなたはあなたが 神に 叫ぶ
dedication of everything that you are to
あなたがさ れ ている すべての献身
the Lord
ザ・ロード
yeah and his presence yeah visits yeah
ええ、彼の存在ええ、 訪問ええ
yeah this is the prayer I made Laurie if
ええ、これは 私がローリーを作った祈りです
you're giving me a life I will serve you
あなたは私に人生を与えています。私はあなたに奉仕します。
for the rest of my life oh my goodness
私の生命の残りのために ああ私の良さ
and so what happened so I started to
何が起こった ので私は
experience the presence of God in that
神の存在を経験する
room and slowly my body started to
部屋はゆっくりと体が始まり ました。
respond shiver with the heavy presence
重い存在に震える
of God which I was experiencing like an
私が経験していた神の
electric shock something the heavy that
その重い 感電 何か
was passing throughout my body and so
私の体に通っていたので
their eyes I experienced a great healing
彼らの目を私は大きな癒しを経験した
and for weeks I have been lying on the
数週間、私は
bed on that moment I was able to sit on
私が座ることができ た その瞬間の ベッド
that bed and the nurses were very much
そのベッドと看護師 は大変だった
surprised so in one encounter at one
1つの 出会いに驚いた
encounter with God in one night one
ある夜の夜に神と出会う
after weeks being like declining yeah
数週間後に衰退するような
you're sitting at silver yeah and the
あなたは ええ銀 で 座っ て います
nurses were waiting was surprised what
看護婦が待っていたのは驚いた
is happening with me and the early
私と早く起きている
morning they took my blood and for the
朝、彼らは私の血をとった
routine checkup
定期的な点検
so so they went and they was very much
そう彼らは行って、彼らは非常にあった
shocked by seeing within one night the
一夜のうちに見るとショックを受けた
medicines were respond not responding on
薬は応答していない
my body within one night what happened
私の体は一夜で 何 が起こったか
to this guy so they did blood work and
この男に、彼らは血液検査をしました。
were there some results oh yeah and what
ああ、何か結果があった
were they saying they were saying that
彼らはそれを言っていた と言いました 。
the there was a sudden shoot up of white
突然の白いシュートアップ が あった
blood cells that had happened to your
あなたに起こっていた血液細胞
body and it is just an what an average
体とそれは ちょうど平均何ですか
person needs and that is your blood
人のニーズとそれはあなたの血です
count now so everything came back to
今すぐカウントして、すべてが戻った
normal yeah every
いつものように
in game metronome now did you feel good
ゲームのメトロノームで今あなたは良い気分になりました
all of a sudden or did it take you a
突然、 あなたに
time to get better or was it just like
良くもそれだけ のよう だった取得する時間
overnight although I want to go home now
私は 今 家に行きたい
just all the night incredible that is
ある だけですべての夜信じられません
incredible for two age of 14 and so you
14 歳の2歳のために信じられないほどです
made a commitment to the Lord
主に約束した
yeah that you would give you'd be all-in
ええ、 あなたは オールインである ことをあなたに与えるだろう
yeah Lord my life is yours yeah did you
ええ、私の人生はあなたのものです。
did you honor that commitment yeah I
私はええ その約束を尊重しませんでした
honor that commitment I went back to the
私は戻ってその約束を尊重
school and they told me that no this
学校 と彼らは私に言った
time because you lost many of the
あなたが多くの
classes you cannot write because the
あなたが書くことができないクラス
indian culture is very much shame
インドの 文化は非常に残念です
oriented culture they don't want to
彼ら が望ん で いない志向の文化
bring shame on the school so if one
学校に恥をもたらすのでもしそうなら
person's no fail in the examination
人は試験に失敗しない
board examination that will be an
ボード審査は
embarrassment for the school yeah so but
学校のための恥ずかしそうなので
I insisted that no the Lord has touched
私は主が触れていないと主張した
me and healed me I'm ready to go I just
私と私を癒して私は行く準備ができている私だけ
want to serve the Lord that was really
本当に 主に奉仕したい
deep in my heart this is the life God
私の心の深いこれは命の神です
has given me and I just want to serve do
私を 与え てくれて、ただ 奉仕 し たい
you think that God not only healed you
あなたは神があなたを癒すだけでなく、
physically but is it possible like did
物理的にそれが 行った ように可能 です
he do something in your spirit like -
彼はあなたの霊で何かをやります。
yes elyda fire calling yeah yeah okay
はいelyda 火は大丈夫ええええ呼び出します
which is so that's what I'm hearing you
それはそうです、私はあなたの話 を 聞いてい ます
say it's like okay I Lord I'll commit
それは大丈夫だと言う私は主が私はコミットします
you but he said okay I'll take you up on
あなたは彼が言ったが大丈夫、私はあなたを連れて行くだろう
this yeah yeah and he deposited
このええええと彼が寄託
something in you that there's a hunger
あなたの中に飢えがあるもの
and I believe that on you're still real
私はあなたがまだ実在していると信じています
today yeah so you were 14 now do you
今日はええ、 今 14歳だったから
mind me asking what's your age now I'm
私は 今、 私は あなたの年齢何を 求めて 気に
turning 30 on this month thirty yell and
今月の30回の 叫び声 と
a happy birthday - yeah this month okay
幸せな 誕生日-ええ、今月大丈夫
so we're talking okay you you've got the
私たちは大丈夫ですか？
we're talking like a 15 year journeys
我々は15年の旅のように話している
yeah just about 15 16 years for you
あなたの ためにちょうど約15 16年
saying yes to the Lord I'm all-in and
私はオールインしています。
your passion to follow his will is as
彼の意志に従うあなたの情熱は
strong today as it was that time yeah so
今日は頑張ったよ
I'd be very interested in hearing about
私は話を聞くに非常に興味があると思い
your journey what happened so you went
あなたの旅は何が起こったのであなたは行った
back to school yeah I went back to the
学校に 戻っ てええ、私は戻って行きました
school and I wrote the examination I got
学校と私は私が持っている試験を書いた
a good grade by the grace of God cuz
神の恵み のcuz によって良いグレード
school wasn't she
学校は彼女ではなかった
okay so you made that look good that's
大丈夫そう、あなたはそれが のことを 良く見せてい ました
good then I came to know that no I can
私が知ることができなかったことが分かりました
do my eleven and twelve the secure
私の 11と12を安全にする
studies and the theological studies
研究と神学研究
together in one of the that is one of
一緒に1つの
the Baptist seminars college back in
バプテストセミナーの大学に戻る
another province which is known as
別の州 として知られている 州
Karnataka they are providing that they
彼らは彼らに彼らが提供しているカルナタカ
have the secular school and theological
世俗的な学校と神学を持つ
school so they are providing that kind
彼らはそのような種類の学校を提供しています
of energy this is fascinating so you're
これは魅力的な エネルギー です
so serious about it that you finish your
それであなたはあなたの
high school and at the same time you
高校と同時にあなたに
also you start your theological training
あなたもあなたの神学的な訓練 を 始める
yeah like that's incredible well friends
ええ 、それは信じられないほどの友人のようです
we're here with Lyn Oh II Samuel yeah
私たちはLyn Oh II Samuel yeahとここにいる
from India the province of Kerala and
インドからはケーララ州と
he's got a wonderful story of the
彼は素晴らしい
provision of God we'll be right back
神 の提供、我々は右戻ってきます
with more from Leno after this stick
この棒の後にレノからもっと多く
around for more for new every day for a
周り のための 新しい毎日のために多くの ため
limited time get your hands on
時間が限られている
limited-edition shirts from the
限定版 シャツから
category-five TV network these
カテゴリ5のテレビネットワーク これら
high-quality shirts are manufactured by
高品質のシャツは、 によって 製造されています
teespring a fundraising website and your
募金の ウェブサイトとあなたを teespring
purchase will help support the shows we
購入がショーを サポートするのに役立ちます
produce get yours today and send us your
今日はあなたのものを作り、 私たちに あなた を送りなさい
pictures to be featured on the
写真は
corresponding show visit cap 5
対応するショー訪問キャップ5
TV slash shirts to support us and get
TV スラッシュシャツ は私たちをサポートして 取得する
your official Network shirt today cat5
あなたの公式ネットワークシャツは今日 cat5
dot TV slash shirts hi we're back with
ドットテレビのスラッシュシャツ
leno Samuel
レノ・サミュエル
oh you hooked me in from the first half
ああ、 あなた は最初の半分から 私を夢中 にした
of this episode about the provision of
このエピソードの提供について
God but I get it could be called the
神様ですが、私はそれが
healing of God it could be called the
神の 癒し はそれを
call of God all of its intertwined
すべて の絡み合った神の呼びかけ
Linda what an exciting testimony you
リンダはあなたに何か刺激的な証言をします
have yeah of course our God is an
もちろん、私たちの神は
exciting God isn't it yeah it's amazing
エキサイティングな神ではないええ、驚くべきことです
what he will do with anyone who says
彼が 言う 人と何をするか
Lord I mean it you asked me to follow
主 よ、あなたが私に従うように頼んだことを意味します
you you said to me in your word if
あなたはあなたの言葉で私に言った
anyone would come after me let him deny
私を 追い詰めると誰もが来ないだろう
himself take up his cross and follow me
自分自身の十字架をつかんで
yeah and Lord you promised to all of us
ええ、主 よ、私たち全員に約束しました
who abandoned to you with everything
すべてのものをあなたに放棄した人
that we are that you would have your
私たち は、あなたが
perfect will in our lives and we were
私たちの生活の中で完璧な意志と私たちは
thankful Lord
感謝の主
I bless you who you're all-in to be
私はあなたが オールインし て いるあなたを祝福します
encouraged today we're with you we're on
今日私たちはあなたと一緒にいることを奨励している
your team we're excited to pray with you
あなたのチームはあなたと一緒に祈ることに興奮しています
but God's best and rich riches for your
あなたのために神の最も豊かな豊かな富
life - it's great yeah soul in oh we
人生 - それは私たちの中で偉大なええの魂です
talked about low blood count like white
白のような低血球数について語った
white blood cells and a miraculous
白血球と奇跡的な
healing and then pursuing when you were
あなたが いた ときに治癒し、追求 する
in grade 11 and 12 however you say yeah
11年生と12年生ですが、
yeah and you were pursuing theology
ええ、あなたは神学を追いかけていた
college at the same time tell us about
同時に 大学は について教えて
that yeah it was a wonderful journey
それは素晴らしい旅でした
like no morning I have the theological
朝のように私は神学を持っている
education afternoon till evening I have
私が持っている夕方までの教育の午後
of secular education so this has been
世俗教育の
combined together and it was a Baptist
一緒に結合し、それはバプテストでした
mission who has been doing that for a
ミッションのためにそれをしてきたミッション
long time in that province okay so your
その州の 長い 時間大丈夫です
school would allow that yeah about that
学校はそれについてええそれを許可します
board in that province food allowed
その州の 食糧を許可されたボード
to happen so so they weren't worried
起こるように彼らは心配していなかった
about that you know that reputation
あなたが その評判 を知っ て いる こと について
knowing like they are not because they
彼らが 彼らの ため に そうでないように知っている
have a great fame of that college
その大学の偉大な名声がある
because one of the missionary has
宣教師の一人が
started that and has produced a lot of
それを開始したと の多くを生産し ています
graduates who are in the top level in
トップレベルにある卒業生
the government sector and almost all of
政府部門 とほぼすべて の
the fields really so even people outside
フィールドは本当に そうで あっても外部の人々
of the church recognize this Theological
教会のこの神学を認識する
College as a good place yeah for
大学は良い場所としてええの ために
learning for our money well isn't that
私たちのお金のための 学習 はそれほど です
great it sounds like the church is
教会のように聞こえる
affecting the culture yeah yeah how cool
どのようにクールな文化ええええに影響を与える
is that okay so now was the workload
それは 大丈夫ですので、今は仕事量でした
heavy
ヘビー
yeah the workload was very heavy because
ワークロードは非常に重かった
I have to maintain both of the
私は両方の
theological studies and a lot of work to
神学研究と多く の
do but God has really honored mean that
しかし、神は本当に光栄に思います。
canvas like I almost all the sub secured
私はほぼすべてのサブのようなキャンバスを確保
subjects I have got academic excellence
私は学業成績が優れている科目
of ADD and and in the theological field
ADDのと 神学の分野
too that is why when we come into a a
あまりにもそれがなぜ私たち が来 たら
life to the Lord is the Lord who is
主に人生は主である主です
taking care of us and leading us forward
私たちの世話をし、 前方 私たちをリードします
and he will really honor us
彼は本当に私たちを敬うでしょう
yeah furnish God you live this Lynn oh I
ええ私はああ 、この リンを 生きる神を提出
know that as I've gotten to know you I
私が得ているとして、あなたに私を知っていることを 知っています
love this well I love who you are I love
これをよく愛する私はあなたが愛している人が大好き
you and I love this part of who you are
あなたと私はあなたが誰なのかこの部分が大好きです
you're welcome sir and thank you it's
あなたは大歓迎です、ありがとうございます
just so good to meet someone who's all
すべての人 に 会うのが とても うれしい
in and to rest in the prove the
証明するため に
provision of the Lord how beautiful this
これはどれくらい美しいのか主の準備
is
は
so we're how did you do how did you do
あなたはどう やってやりましたか？
in your 11th and 12th year in the
あなたの11 年 目と12 年目に
theology yeah I I didn't well land I
神学Ⅱ私はうまくいっていなかった
have graduated from there endure with
そこ から卒業 した
the good grades and all my teachers were
良い成績と私の先生はすべて
very were very much happy about me and
非常に私について 非常に 満足 し てい た と
they were telling me that no you can
彼らは私に あなたができないと 言っ ていた
excel in your studies and get to the
あなたの研究に秀でて、
know if within short period of time do
短期間であれば知っている
as much as education you can that's the
教育と同じように、それはあなたの
way however cultural works and so they
文化的なやり方の ように
were encouraging me there in that level
そのレベルで私をそこに励ましてくれました
good and congratulations you didn't oh
あなたはああ、おめでとうとおめでとう
yeah
ええ
and so your mom and dad they were happy
あなたのお母さんとお父さん が幸せだったので
obviously yeah they were very happy
明らかにええ、彼らはとても幸せだった
about it
それについて
yeah great so they were one of the thing
ええ素晴らしい ので、彼らは もの の一つでした
that they
彼らは
president while I was receiving all
私が すべて を 受けていた ときの大統領
these academic excellence and that for
これらの学術の卓越性と そのための
all the department like sociology
社会学のような すべての部門
history and everything so they were
歴史とそのすべてがそうだった
there and they were so happy about it
そこに彼らはそれ について とても幸せ だった
boy and now I know you and sounds to me
私はあなたと私のことを知っている
like God was preparing you to for a
神があなたの ために あなた を準備していたように
future because you've got these ok these
あなたがこれらの 大丈夫 を持っているので、将来
subjects you just talked about that you
あなたがちょうど話した主題
did well in what was your next step
あなたの次のステップだったものでうまくいった
after you your it look like tell me yeah
あなたの後にそれは私のええを言うように見える
as a high school do you call it god
高校としてあなたはそれを 神 と呼んでいますか？
that's a high school and so from there I
それは高校なので、そこから
have graduated and I went back to my
卒業 して私に戻っ た
province and I was waiting upon what to
州と私は何を待っていた
do whether I have to go for the theology
私が神学のために行く必要があるかどうか
education or because I felt the need it
教育や私はそれを必要と感じたので
wasn't just an Associated biblical
関連する聖書だけではありませんでした
studies just covering almost all the it
ほとんどすべてをカバーするだけの研究
is very much related to the biblical
聖書に非常に 関連 して いる
studies you know studying the Word of
あなたが研究していることを知っている研究
God and everything so I felt the need
神と私はすべての必要性を感じたので
that I need more training so I was
私はもっと練習が必要なので
waiting upon the Lord and then Lord
主を待ってから主よ
brought a servant of God who has just
神だけの僕を持って来た
graduated from a Bible College and he
聖書 カレッジ を 卒業し、 彼は
was going to pioneer a mission in
ミッションを先駆けて
somewhere near to my province and so he
私の州のどこか近くにいるので
invited me and I became part of that oh
私を招待し、私 はその あ あの 一部 と なった
wait a second so you mean a minister
あなたが 大臣 を意味するので、秒を待つ
invited you to come and partner with
あなたと来てパートナーに招待しました
yeah Minister yeah ok and did I get this
はい大臣大丈夫と 私はこれを得た
you said you went back to your province
あなたはあなた の道 に 戻った と述べました
yeah did you go away for yeah yeah yeah
ええ、 ええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええ
it's away from your family yeah every
それはあなたの家族から 離れて いる
from my family I know all a 14-year
私の家族からは、 私は すべて14年間 を知ってい ます
55:14 oh my goodness I missed that part
55:14ああ私の良さ私は その 部分 を逃し た
okay cuz I'm like what you came back
さて、あなた が戻った もののようなものです
yeah okay so that's incredible so you're
うん、それは信じられないほどです
studying grade 11 and 12 and theology at
11年生と12年生を学び、
the age of 15 you heard this away from
あなたは 、この離れて から 聞いた15 歳
your parent from my pattern and that was
あなたの親は私のパターンから、 それは
a two-year journey yeah - yeah journey
2年の旅、 ええ、ええの 旅
okay so now you're what 17 same come
大丈夫そう今は17が 同じ来る 何です
back home saying I think I need more
私は もっと 必要と思うと言って帰宅
training yeah and this missionary guy or
トレーニングのええとこの宣教師の
a church planter or whatever it is is I
教会プランターやそれが何であれ私は
want and you joined him that has giant
欲しいとあなた は巨人を持つ 彼に加わった
an oh my god well what you do
ああ、私の神 よ、あなたがすること
what this is fascinating it was so tough
これは何が魅力的なのか、 それはとても厳しいものでした
I would say that being in the mission
私はその使命にいると言います
field when you start a pioneer world
パイオニアの世界を始めるときのフィールド
especially back in my country it's just
特にバック私の国では それだけです
a developing country so the things were
開発途上国であったので、
very much minimal and the society were
非常に極小で、 社会は
very much hostile and as we reach with
非常に敵対的で、我々が
the gospel message but we had the
福音のメッセージが、私たちは
opening and there was a church right now
今すぐ教会がありました
which is growing and we have almost 200
それ は成長しており、私たちはほぼ 200
people attending that church has been
その教会 に出席 している 人々 は
pioneered today in 2018 these like 15
今日の2018年に開拓された
years later 15 years like 30 whatever
何年も後の 15 年は 30 年後
yeah yeah oh my good and you you were
ええええああ、私は良いとあなた あなたがいました
the pioneers yeah yeah yes how does that
パイオニアはい 、ええ、ええ か ということ ありません
feel to know that there's two hundred
200人 がいることを知りたい
believers worshiping the Lord today
信者は今日主を崇拝する
it's amazing we do not know even if it
たとえそれがわからなくても驚くべきことです
is small a small effort from our side
私たちの側からの小さな努力です
when we take by faith and we put the
私たちが信仰によって抱くと、 私たちは
scene or how it will know how God God is
神の神がどのようになっているかを知る方法
the one who produced the fruit right so
果物を正しく 生産した人
we are just sowing the seed and it was
私たちはただ種をまき、それは
so wonderful to see that life continued
人生が続く ことを見てとても素晴らしい
a very lively congregation I would say
私が言う非常に活発な集会
worshiping the Lord in truth and spirit
真実と精神で主を礼拝する
excites me listening to this story now
今この話を 聞い て興奮する
you mentioned something about sowing
あなたは播種について何か言及した
seed and you mentioned something about
あなたは何かを言った
opposition yeah okay tell me like what
野党ええ、 大丈夫何かのように教えてください
so what did you do because you're with
あなたと一緒にいるので、 あなたは何をしましたか？
this man maybe ever this man we used to
この男はたぶん、私たちがこれまで慣れてきたこの男
have a morning prayer walk which we used
私たちが使った朝の祈りの散歩があります
to know surround the places and just
場所 を 囲む だけで 知っている
pray for the families and as we pass by
家族のために祈ると、私たちは通り過ぎるよう
the two houses which are just on the way
ちょうど 向こうにある 2 つの家
we just bless them and we pray that Lord
私たちはそれらを祝福し、 私たち は 主 に祈る
let them know the love of Christ Jesus
彼らにキリスト・イエスの愛を知らせてください
that's what we did and and then we went
それが私たちがやったことです
with of some of the messages the tracks
いくつかのメッセージのトラック
we call like the messages and we just if
私たちはメッセージのように呼びます。
somebody's hearing willing to listen to
に 耳を傾け て喜んで誰かの公聴会
it we share the gospel with now did you
私たちは 今 、福音を共有し ています
go and knock on their door yes all
行くと彼らのドアをノックする はいすべて
contact oh you would just yeah how are
ああ、ちょうどええ、 連絡 方法
you
君は
and and before you're knocking and even
あなたがノッキングしていなくても
maybe as you're talking you're praying
多分あなたが 話しているようにあなたは祈っている
yeah cheering yeah
はい、応援しています
so what we use to do is that now we pray
私たちがしているのは、 今私たちが祈っていることです
as we when we go for the morning walk we
私たちが朝の散歩に行くとき、私たちは
pray for and leave when we feel that
私たちがそれを感じるときに祈り、去ります
there is a leading of the Spirit within
そこには スピリットがあります
ourselves we go to those houses and just
私たち自身がそれらの家に行き、 ちょうど
knock at that door so you wait until the
あなたがされるまで待つように、 そのドアにノック
Lord yeah
主よ
gives you a promise yeah prompting and
あなたにプロンプ​​トを出す
did you find that was helpful yeah that
あなたはそれが ええことを 役立った見つけました
was very helpful because there will be
そこにあるので非常に有用だった
some well I think so if my memory is
私の記憶が
right that was one family which was
右のそれだっ た 一つの家族 でした
going through some tough time in their
彼らの 中でいくつかの厳しい時を経 て
life and they were thinking of ending up
人生と彼らは終わることを考えていた
their life and we were there just
彼らの人生と私たちはちょうどそこにいた
knocking up their door and no sharing
彼らのドアをノックアウトし、共有しない
this wonderful message of hope to their
彼らに 希望のこの素晴らしいメッセージ
life and so they embrace the Christ know
人生とは、彼らが知っているキリストを受け入れる
and they came they were the first I
彼らが来たのは彼らが最初の私だった
think yeah they were the first who came
彼らが来た最初の人だと思う
to our church so here this young
私たちの教会にここで若い
teenager and God leads you to a family
ティーンエイジャーと神があなたを 家族に 導いてくれます
that's thinking it's time to end it all
それはそれをすべて終了する時だと思っている
yeah and it all I can't wait I'm so glad
ええ、 それはすべて私が待つことができない私はとても 嬉しいです
you're gonna be with us for another
あなたはつもり 別のための私達と一緒にしています
episode but in the in the short time
エピソードではなく、 短期間で
that we've got left yeah why don't we
我々は 左の 持っていることをええ 、なぜ 私たちには ありません
talk to our viewers maybe there's
私たち 視聴者 に話かもしれない があります
somebody here listening today who feels
ここで誰かが今日聞いている誰かが感じる
like that's life isn't worth living yeah
そのようええ 人生は 生きる価値 はないのです
could you could you what would you say
あなたは何 を言う だろう か？
to them today Linda would you would you
彼らに今日 リンダ はあなたに
speak to them no God will bring in our
何の神が私たちにもたらしていないだろう 彼らに 話します
life into God will lead us into
神への人生は私たち を
different situations or circumstances in
さまざまな状況 や状況
our life and I believe that any crucial
私たちの生活と私は すべての非常に重要 と考えてい
situation that you phrase in your life
あなたの人生におけるフレーズの状況
it is an opportunity to meet and
会うチャンスです
experience the love of God in your life
あなたの 人生 で神の愛を体験してください
and which I have seen in my ministry
私の 奉仕で 見たことがある
those people who are very hot loss in
で非常に熱い 損失している人々
their life and the Jesus Christ is the
彼らの人生とイエス・キリストは
one who can give true hop into your life
あなたの人生に 真のホップを与えることができる人
and to carry on in your life he will
あなたの人生を続けるためには、彼は
give you the strength to push on in that
あなたに力を入れて
difficult circumstance should we ask him
困難な状況は 、我々は彼に尋ねるべき
to invite him what do we
私たちに何をするのか、彼 を 招待する
how do we get him to be the one that
どのように我々は彼が その 一つであること が 入手できますか
does that leaner what would we do you
それは私たちがあなたに何をしてくれるのでしょうか？
just pray to God a simple prayer you you
単純な祈りをあなたに教えてください
don't have to be have a big theological
大きな神学を持つ必要はありません
jargons you have to put in that in that
あなたはその中に入れなければならない専門用語
prayer just pray to God Lord this is
祈りは、 ちょうど これが 神、主に祈ります
what I was facing in my life Lord you
私の人生で直面していたこと主よ
are a living God come to my life this is
生きている 神が私の人生に来る
the situation which I am facing and I
私が直面している状況と私
have heard that nothing is impossible to
何も不可能ではないと聞いた
God I truly believe that lot Here I am
神 本当にそれを信じている 私はここにいる
giving my circumstances and leaving my
私の状況を 与え て、私を 残す
life in tonight and Lord come into my
今夜の生活と私の中に来る
life
生活
praise God Lynn oh thank you so much for
神リンを賛美してああああああああありがとう
sharing the first part of an amazing
驚くべきことの最初の部分を共有する
calling a healing from Almighty God and
全能の 神 からの癒しを呼び
his provision just the same god bless
彼の規定はまったく同じ 神の祝福
you everyone we'll see you again next
あなたは、誰も私たちは あなたにもう一度、次を 参照してくださいよ
week
週間
catch a new episode of new every day
毎日新しいの新しいエピソードをキャッチ
every Friday morning at new every day TV
毎週金曜日の朝 、新しい毎日の テレビで
we're also on roku Kodi
私たちは、Rokuの コディ にもしています
Plex youtube google play music podcasts
Plex youtube googleの 音楽ポッドキャストを再生する
and news book or if you're in Southern
あなたが 南部に いれば
California tune in every Sunday morning
毎週日曜日にカリフォルニア州で調整する
at 6:30 on kbdb TV channel 33 television
kbdbのテレビチャンネル33のテレビで6:30 に
for the high desert
高い砂漠のために
[Music]
[音楽]